Guide to the Les K. Wright papers and Bear History Project files, 1959-2010.
Wright, Les K. papers and Bear History Project files, 1959-2010
- Series IV. Bear History Project
  - Bear Clipping Files
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Vanity Plates Project - Assorted Photos, 1990s (Box 71, Folder 67-68)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Vanity Plates Project - Layout, 1990s (Box 71, Folder 69)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Vanity Plates Project - Victor Hedrick, n.d. (Box 71, Folder 70)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Vanity Plates Project - Eric Lein, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 71)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Vanity Plates Project - Gregory Meholic, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 72)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Vanity Plates Project - Craig Nielsen, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 73)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Vanity Plates Project - David Nigro, 1998 (Box 71, Folder 74)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Vanity Plates Project - Alan Opel, 1998 (Box 71, Folder 75)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Vanity Plates Project - Bob "Bear" Sigmon, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 76)
    - Bear Clipping: Truckers, 2001 (Box 71, Folder 77)
    - Bear Clipping: Wolf-Man, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 78)
    - Bear Clipping: Townsend, Larry, 2008 (Box 71, Folder 79)
    - Bear Clipping: Event Flyers and Advertisement Quartercards, 2000s (Box 71, Folder 80)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Postcards and Photos, ca. 1995 (Box 71, Folder 81)
    - Bear Clipping: Masculinity and Sexuality, 1996-2007 (Box 71, Folder 82)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Event Programs and Publications, 1999-2009 (Box 71, Folder 83)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Articles, 1996-2005 (Box 71, Folder 84)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Articles, 2000s (Box 52, Folder 23-25)
    - Bear Clipping: Events, 2000s (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Bear Clipping: Bear Representations, 2000s (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Bear Clipping: Articles about Transgenders, 2000s (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Bear Clipping: Teddy Bears, 2000s (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Bear Clipping: Les Wright, 1995, 2000, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 30-31)
- Series V. Nashoba Institute
  - Steering e-group, 2000-2002 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Think Tank Website communication, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Nashoba Institute misc., mainly correspondence, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - AMSA (American Men's Studies Association), 1998-2001 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Art & Artists Collection, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 46-47)
  - Bear Health, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Bear Health Project, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Bear Health Project Website 4.0, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Gay & Lesbian Mental Health, 1997(?) (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - GMHS (Gay Men's Health Summits), various, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - History & Archive (Bear History Project), 2001 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Kadour, Ric Kasini and Byrne, Chris correspondence, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - McDiarmid, Bob, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Men's Resource Center Annual Retreat, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Men's Studies, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Noble, John, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Social Change, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - NOMAS (National Organization for Men Against Sexism), 2004 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - NOMSV (National Organization of Male Sexual Victimization), 2001-2003 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Kasini House/Nashoba Board (Box 27)
  - Board retreat-organizing efforts (Box 27)
  - Kasini House contract, June 2003 (Box 27)
  - Steering eGroup, 2004 (Box 27)
  - Nashoba Board, May 2003-May 2004; 11 folders (Box 27)
  - nashobainstitute.org (Box 27)
  - bearhistory.com domain names (Box 27)
  - Archives/BHP (Box 27)
  - Health (Box 27)
  - Art and artists (Box 27)
  - Web site development (Box 27)
  - Fundraising (Box 27)
  - Nashoba Artists Collective (Box 27)
  - Mailing list messages (Box 27)
  - O'Kelly, Erin, University of New Hampshire (Box 27)
  - "Dark Corners", online novel, Verisimilitude 1,2,3 (Box 27)
  - Verisimilitude 1-3, 2002-2003; 4 folders (Box 27)
  - Burns, Rory Sean, SSM/AIDS, Verisimilitude 4 (Box 27)
  - Verisimilitude 5-6, 3 folders (Box 27)
  - Bear Club officers forum, closed eGroup (Box 27)
  - Homo/Macho Vermont, 2004; 2 folders (Box 27)
  - Homo/Macho transformations, BCA Visiting Curators program, 2002-2003 (Box 27)
  - Erotic art webring (Box 27)
  - Bear Icons, Los Angeles (Box 27)
  - Adonis Art Gallery (Box 27)
  - Manstouch Gallery (Box 27)
  - Fundraising (Box 27)
  - Public relations (Box 27)
  - Articles "on hold" (Box 27)
  - Source/contacts to follow up (Box 27)
  - Health: AIDS, mental, physical (Box 27)
  - Islam-Turkey (Box 27)
  - Germany (Box 27)
  - Verisimilitude 1:2 (Box 27)
  - "Thinking Bear Gazette" online journal (Box 27)
  - Thinking Bear magazine (Box 27)
  - Friend and family solicitation (Box 27)
  - Business sponsorships (Box 27)
  - Bisexual Resource Center contract (Box 27)
  - General information (Box 27)
  - Bylaws (Box 27)
  - Pride Foundation (Box 27)
  - Out Fund/FEX (Box 27)
  - Haymarket Fund (Box 27)
  - Bear Club solicitation (Box 27)
  - Neither Leather nor Lace, University of New Hampshire (Box 27)
  - Midwest Bears (Box 27)
  - Incorporation (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
  - Bank papers (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Incorporation (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - EIN (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Charitas (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Donations (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - By-Laws (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Articles of Organization (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Form 1023 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Fiscal Agreement with Bisexual Resource Center (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Redevelopment, 2007 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Bear Icon Artist Collective (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Homo/Macho (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Origin of Nashoba (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - BHP Correspondence (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Report to Kasini House, June 2003 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - HIV Writing Group (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Miscellany, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Castro articles (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Bear Icons Slide show (Box 55, Folder 21-22)
  - Bear Spirit/A Bear Life, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Bear theory (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Bear Pride (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Bears, Icons and hypermasculine desire (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Essays about masculinity (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Articles of Gay and lesbian review (Box 55, Folder 28-29)
  - Articles about Bears (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Articles of White Crane (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Articles (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Articles of Voice Male (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Articles of San Francisco Bay Times (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Neither leather nor lace project (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Manifesting Bear Community (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Tangled memories of a wounded storyteller (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence:Sergio Mobilia (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence:B. William Schlinder, 2009-2010 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence:Mike Simpson (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence:Rich Stadmiller (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence:William Stewart (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence:Dave Thompson (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence:Janice Threm (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence:Daniel Von Brighoff (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence:Bill Ward (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence:Steve Klein (Box 55, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence:Tony Larson (Box 55, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence:Jim Lawer, 2009 (Box 55, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence:Carl Lawrence (Box 55, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence:Erik Kristensen (Box 55, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence:Scott LaGreca (Box 55, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence:Randolph Langenrach (Box 55, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence:Ruth Lehmann (Box 55, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence:Tom Libry (Box 55, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence:Bob Maidel, 2004-2009 (Box 55, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence:Robert McDiarmid (Box 55, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence:Drew Bourn (Box 55, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence:Dennis Blanchard (Box 55, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence:Jeffrey Dickemann (Box 55, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence:John Benet (Box 55, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence:Bill Benemann (Box 55, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence:George Bailey (Box 55, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence:Billie Aul (Box 55, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence:Allan Arnaboldi (Box 55, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence:Thomas Arend (Box 55, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence:Andy (Box 55, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence:Bill Amplo (Box 55, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence:Juseis Cibuls (Box 55, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence:Brent Calderwood (Box 55, Folder 70)
  - Brent Calderwood Pictures (Box 55, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence:Joe and Chris Browning (Box 55, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence:Randy Bowman (Box 55, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence:Scott Johnson (Box 55, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence:Bob Hirshberg (Box 55, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence:Brian (Box 55, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence:Oliver Glover (Box 55, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence:Sam Ganczaruck (Box 55, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence:Jack Fritscher (Box 55, Folder 79)
  - Correspondence:Bob Ebersole (Box 55, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence:Alan Eakin (Box 55, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence:Dale Wehrle (Box 55, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence:Wright Family (Box 55, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence:Les Wright (Box 55, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence:Phil (Box 55, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence:Many postcards (Box 55, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence:Bill Palmer (Box 55, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence:Ken Ratcyffei (Box 55, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence:Marc Morris (Box 55, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence:Vinny De Virgilis (Box 55, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence:Simon Goodman (Box 55, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence:Kevin Harding (Box 55, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence:Johnathan Heller (Box 55, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence:Marcus Womscott (Box 55, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence:Steve Heyl (Box 55, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence:John Evans (Box 55, Folder 96)
  - Christmas 2004 (Box 55, Folder 98)
  - Christmas 2005 (Box 55, Folder 99)
  - Christmas 2006 (Box 55, Folder 100)
  - Christmas 2007 (Box 55, Folder 101)
  - Christmas 2008 (Box 55, Folder 102)
  - Christmas 2009 (Box 55, Folder 103)
  - Negatives (Box 55, Folder 104)
  - Brent Calderwood Pictures, CD-743 (Box 55)
  - Love!Valour!Compassion!, DVD 607-608 (Box 55)
  - Correspondence: J. West Hardin, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence: Mushtatov, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence: Paul R. Tompkins, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence: Gianni Rauso, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 108)
- Series VI. Audiovisual and Computer Media
  - "What is a Bear?", February 15-16, 1992; 2 cassette audiotapes (Box 14)
  - "What is a Bear?" Bear Expo, February 13, 1993; Cassette audiotape (Box 14)
  - "Group Dynamics" Bear Expo, February 13, 1993; Cassette audiotape (Box 14)
  - "What is a Bear?", February 19, 1994; Cassette audiotape (Box 14)
  - Interview with Steve Dyer, May 31, 1995; Cassette audiotape (Box 14)
  - John Rand, Interview for Bear Book, January 28, 1996; Cassette audiotape (Box 14)
  - Reed Wilgoren, January 2000; Cassette audiotape (Box 14)
  - International Bear Contest, Tom Ammiano, Pussy Tourette, February 16-18, 1996; 8mm video cassette (Box 14)
  - Ben Brumer- Bear Hugs, Bear Expo, July 30, 1996; 8mm (Box 14)
  - Mike Simmons- Bear Book 2, 8mm (Box 14)
  - Bear Book 2- Original Docs in MS Word format, August 29, 1999; CD-3531
  - Bears Mailing List 38-590, BML 2 2-365, Text files about Bears, Bear Web Pages, DVD-2387
  - LKW Dissertation (1 envelope), Floppy disks (Box 14)
  - LKW- CV, Articles, Drafts, Journals, FD-417-FD-436; Floppy disks
  - Bear Mailing List, FD-374-FD-406; Floppy disks
  - Bear History, FD-407-FD-416; Floppy disks
  - Correspondence, FD-437-FD-476; Floppy disks
  - Maturango Museum, Sylvia Winslow Gallery - John Rand Photography, 2003; V-6032 (Box 14)
  - Bear Expo Highlights, 1992-1993; V-474
  - Naked, Hairy, Homo Smut, 1993; V-475
  - International Mr. Bear Competition, 1994; V-476
  - International Mr. Bear Contest, 1995; V-477
  - BHP: Steve Dyer Interview, 1995; V-478
  - Mr. Front Range Bear Competition, 1995; V-479
  - International Bear Rendezvous, 1995; V-480
  - Mr. Southern California Bear Contest, 1996; V-481
  - International Mr. Bear Competition, 1996; V-482
  - Mr. Southern California Bear Contest, 1997; V-483
  - Mr. Southern California Bear Contest, 1998; V-484
  - 1998, V-485
  - Interview- LKW Bear Icons art exhibit, 2000; V-486
  - Lurch in his Environment, 2000; V-487
  - Men of the Midway, V-488
  - Men of SF4, V-489
  - Mr. Rocky Mountain Bear Contest, 1994; V-5504 (Box 62)
  - The Bear Sampler, V-5505 (Box 62)
  - Bear Expo '94, 1994; V-5506 (Box 62)
  - Bear Bust, 1994; V-5507 (Box 62)
  - Mr. Front Range Bear Competition, 1995; V-5508 (Box 62)
  - Mr. Southern California Bear Contest, 1994; V-5509 (Box 62)
  - Goatboy and the Music Machines, 1997; V-5510 (Box 62)
  - The 1997 International Mr. Bear Competition, V-5511 (Box 62)
  - The Wright in the 1960's, V-5512 (Box 62)
  - Woof: The Bear Film, V-5513 (Box 62)
  - Fichburg, MA, V-5514 (Box 62)
  - Lurch On Video, V-5515 (Box 62)
  - Castro Street: Paula Lichtenberg, 1996; V-5523 (Box 62)
  - Castro Street: Danny McCloskey, 1996; V-5524 (Box 62)
  - Castro Street: Ron Williams and Dwight Stevers, 1996; V-5525/V-5527 (Box 62)
  - Castro Street: Buzz Taylor, 1996; V-5526 (Box 62)
  - Castro Street: Tom Libby, 1996; V-5528 (Box 62)
  - Castro Street: Carl Lawrence, 1996; V-5529 (Box 62)
  - Castro Street: Keith Schroeder, 1996; V-5530 (Box 62)
  - Castro Street: Trevor Hailey, 1996; V-5531 (Box 62)
  - Castro Street: David Gaskin, 1996; V-5532 (Box 62)
  - Castro Street: Tom Holt, 1996; V-5533 (Box 62)
  - Castro Street: Jack Fertig, 1996; V-5534-V-5535 (Box 62)
  - Nikos Diamon, 1999; V-5536-V-5538 (Box 62)
  - dan Nicoletta, 1999; V-5539 (Box 62)
  - Burt Gerris, 1999; V-5540 (Box 62)
  - LKW: Trip Tv San Francisco, 1996; V-5541 (Box 62)
  - Bearatones, tr-8751a (Box 62)
  - Joe Towner and MCO/Bill Jones, 1984; tr-8752a (Box 62)
  - Rob Tielman, 1986; tr-8753a (Box 62)
  - Jean Pierre Dumas/Jean Claude Lemste, 1986; tr-8754a (Box 62)
  - George Sued, 1986; tr-8755a/tr8756a (Box 62)
  - Theo Van Der Meer, 1986; tr-8757a (Box 62)
  - Manfred Herzer, 1986; tr-8758a (Box 62)
  - Michiel Bollinger, 1984; tr-8759a (Box 62)
  - Aids and Mythologies / Aids and Politics, 1987; tr-8760a (Box 62)
  - Social Construction of Homosexuality, 1987; tr-8761a (Box 62)
  - Aids in the mind of America / Normal Heart, 1987; tr-8762a (Box 62)
  - Normal Heart II / Illness as metaphor, 1987; tr-8762a (Box 62)
  - Rob Tielman, 1987; tr-8764a (Box 62)
  - Van Der Meer "Sodomitical Subculture in Holland", 1988; tr-8765a (Box 62)
  - Castro Street Interviews, 1992; tr-8766a/tr-8767a (Box 62)
  - Bud Vadon, 1992; tr-8768a (Box 62)
  - Outwrite writer's Conference, 1993; tr-8769a-tr-8774a (Box 62)
  - The Positive AIDs Connection, 1995; tr-8775a (Box 62)
  - HIV Prevention, 1995-1996; tr-8776a (Box 62)
  - Martin Swinger, 1984; tr-8777a (Box 62)
  - RFSL Interview, 1984; tr-8778a/tr-8779 (Box 62)
  - Mount Ida, 1993; Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Research, 1993; Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Mount Ida, 1994-1996; Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Jpg's, 1997; Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Nashoba Institute, 1997; Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Mount Ida, 1997; Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Lazy Bear Weekend, 1998; Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Mount Ida, 1998; Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Worcester State, 1998; Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Gay Sexuality and Spirituality Talk, 1998; Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - BHP-Lynn Ludwig Photos, 1998; Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Dore Alley Fair, 1998; Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Lazy Bear Weekend, 1998; Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Mount Ida, 1999; Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Sabbatical, 2001; Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Bear Health, 2003; Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Castro Street: Gay Hometown, USA, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Castro History, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Bear Icons, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - A Bear reader, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Bears, typologies and masculinities, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Castro Street: Oral Histories, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Dutch Gay Lit 1,2,3, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Bear Icons Disk II, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Bear Documentary, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Mount Ida Special (Journal), Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - "Female" Trouble, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Alan and Rob, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Catastrophic fiction, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - National Center of Death Education, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Bear Icons Slide Show, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Bear Icons Slide Show NYC, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Germanictic Gay Culture and Lit, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - J. Palmer Series 2, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - J. S. Adams - images/.jpgs, Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Damien Costilla - images, One Zip Floppy disks (Box 63)
  - Sausalito and Brent Calderwood, 2007; CD-744
  - BC in Dolores Parla, 2007; CD-745
  - Casa Diamante, 2007; CD-746
  - Guernaville, 2007; CD-746
  - BC Vivdresses, 2007; CD-758
  - Buent and les, 2007; CD-759
  - Brent Calderwood, 2007; CD-760
  - Les and Kevin, 2007; CD-761
  - Bear Icons II, CD-762
  - Images 2000-2001 Bear Icons, CD-763
  - B12 Images, 2000; CD-764
  - BIAC, 2002; CD-765
  - Bear Icons II, CD-766-CD-768
  - Homo/Macho VT, 2004; CD-769
  - Submission for Homo Macho/Eroticizing Masculinities, 2002-2004; CD-770 (Box 64)
  - Homo Macho A Submission from Bruce Eves, CD-7771 (Box 64)
  - www.art4bears.com, CD-772
  - Chris Komater, CD-773
  - BIAC Trio, CD-774
  - Tom Hudgins Art and Design, CD-775
  - My idea of fun. Bruce Evers, 2002; CD-776
  - BLK W/ Bear, CD-777 (Box 64)
  - Tasty, 2003; CD-778
  - 1001 Arabian Nights, CD-779
  - Homo / Macho Transformations, 2002; CD-780
  - Bear Icons 2, CD-781 (Box 64)
  - Gianorso samples for Homo Macho, 2004; CD-782
  - Kurt files Text and Artwork, 2002; CD-783
  - BIAC 2, CD-784
  - Les' Picks for Exhibition, CD-785
  - David Greig, CD-786-CD-787
  - 30 Images for Publication, CD-788
  - Bear Tiffs, CD-789
  - Homo Macho, CD-790
  - Tim Goecke, CD-791
  - Homo Macho Application, CD-792
  - Neil Bruce Art, CD-793
  - Thinking Bear Trading Co., CD-794
  - Thinking Bear Trading Co. Bear Art., CD-795
  - Hot House Showcase, 2007; DVD-689 (Box 64)
  - Best of RichTrove 2007, DVD-690 (Box 64)
  - International Mr. Leather, 2007; DVD-691 (Box 64)
  - 2007 Intl Ms. Leather Contest, DVD-692 (Box 64)
  - San Francisco leather, DVD-693 (Box 64)
  - Homo / Macho VT, CD-796-CD-798
  - Homo / Macho VT, CD-799-CD-802
  - Curator Mails, CD-796
  - Nashoba Institute, 2003; CD-810
  - Neither leather nor lace, 2003; CD-811
  - Nashoba, 2006; CD-803-CD-807
  - BIAC, CD-808
  - Nashoba Art, 2007; CD-812-CD-813
  - Photos, 2004; CD-814
  - March, 2004; CD-815
  - Nashoba Art, CD-816-CD-817
  - Bear History Project, 2006; CD-818
  - Photos, 2004; CD-819-CD-827
  - Photos, 2005; CD-828-CD-841
  - Photos, 2006; CD-842-CD-847
  - Photos, 2007; CD-848-CD-849
  - The Cottage, DVD-685
  - Photos by Kelin Harding, 2008; DVD-686
  - Tale of Bears, DVD-623
  - Dore Alley Street Fair, DVD-625
  - Photos, 2005; CD-849-CD-861
  - Photos, 2006; CD-862-CD-871
  - Photos, 2004; CD-872-CD-876
  - Desktop Backup, 2002; CD-877-CD-880
  - Verisimilitude, 2003; CD-881-CD-882
  - The Cottage, CD-883-CD-884
  - Everyday Heroes, 2007; CD-885
  - Live Journal, 2006; CD-886-CD-887
  - March, 11, 2004; CD-888
  - Mark R. Choston, CD-889
  - SFBA, 2004; CD-890-CD-892
  - Billy Gathering, 2007; CD-893
  - Billy Gathering, 2009; CD-894
  - Neither leather nor lace, 2003; CD-895
  - IBR, 2004; CD-896
  - Octobearfest Logos, CD-897
  - Homo / Macho VT, 2007; CD-796
  - BHP, CD-898-CD-902
  - Mount Ida College Files, 2006; CD-903
  - The Bear, CD-904
  - Thesis Document, 2003; CD-905
  - Asking to see the soul, CD-906-CD-908
  - Male Nudes, 2004; CD-909
  - Fred Lopez, 2007; CD-910
  - Tom Oakleys Stuff, CD-911
  - Brent Calderwood, DVD-684
  - Les Wright Photos, CD-961
  - Microsoft Money film, 1998-2003; CD-962
  - Bears Television Workshop, DVD-624
  - Active Projects, CD-912
  - Charger, CD-913
  - Address Book Pam, CD-914
  - Castro Country Club, CD-915
  - DRW, CD-916
  - Hubert Kennedy, CD-917
  - Nashoba Files, CD-918-CD-919
  - My docs, CD-920-CD-925
  - Nashoba, CD-926-CD-929
  - Mount Ida and Academic C.V., CD-930
  - Art Collection, CD-931
  - Personal Web Pages, CD-932
  - Verisimilitude 2, CD-933-CD-935
  - Manuscripts, CD-937
  - LKW personal, CD-938
  - Mount Ida 2002, CD-939
  - My music, CD-940
  - Bear in Mind, CD-941-CD-948
  - Ing Music, CD-948b-CD-957 (Box 64)
  - Ing Music, CD-957 (Box 64)
  - Rothko.BLK w/Bear Music, CD-949 (Box 64)
  - TechnoBears Music, CD-950-CD-952
  - Damian Music, CD-953 (Box 64)
  - Martin Swinger Music, CD-954-CD-956 (Box 64)
  - Vision of a Bear, CD-958 (Box 64)
  - Joseph Victor Sieger, CD-959 (Box 64)
  - Giulio Lucente Works, 1980-2001; CD-1844
  - Rand Riccoboni - 3 Bears, 2002; CD-1845
  - Beard of Joseph Palmer Series Two, CD-1846
  - Raw footage for 1993 Bear documentary., [8mm videotape]; John Topping
    - Cascade Bears, Prowl 93, 2 tapes (Box 31)
    - River Bears, Cincinnati (Box 31)
    - Columbus Ursine Brotherhood; Scott Hill, Bears on Bikes (Box 31)
    - New England Bears; Bears mailing list (Box 31)
    - Bluegrass Bears; Paul Smith... (Box 31)
    - Shawn Smith, North Country Bears; Larry Toothman (5 min.) (Box 31)
    - Richard Bulger; Ben Bruner (Box 31)
    - Les Wright-Bear History Project (Box 31)
    - Bear it in the Desert; Satyrs; Bears LA; rest stop stretch (Box 31)
    - Folsom Street Fair; Peter Barry lip sync; Clark and Keith lip sync; Utah rest stop; OctoBEARfest; Larry Toothman (Box 31)
    - Great Lakes Bears Chicago; Joe Policarpio (Box 31)
    - Southern Bears-Atlanta; Bear Bust-Florida (Box 31)
    - West Florida Growlers; Bears Old Pueblo (Box 31)
    - Jay Johnson; Bear store; Jim Burch; Ben Bruner and Bill Martin (Box 31)
    - Pacific Bears-Guerneville; Smokey Bear; Jeff (Halls?); Lunch (Box 31)
    - Darrel and Sam-San Francisco; Northwest Bears-Seattle; Sugar Bear interview; Walt and Danny lip sync; Seattle skyline (Box 31)
    - New York - Chris Xefos, Lenny Waller (Box 31)
    - Hank Becker-DC; Confederate Bears-North Carolina (Box 31)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
The following materials have been separated from the collection. Some may have been cataloged individually:
Diary of a Thought Criminal 1996 book, signed by author Mark I. Chester "For Les, to a fellow traveller. 10/13/96", HSX TR676 .C52 + c.2
100 Percent Beef. issue 1-7 (2002-2003:May); issue 12-16 (2004); issue 17-19 (2005:Jan, March, May);issue 31 (2007); issue 40-43 (2008)
A Bear's Life. Issue 1 (2005: Summer); issue 11 (2008: Spring); issue 19 (2010: Spring)
AIDS The Literacy Response. By Emmanuel S.Nelson (1992)
American Bear. Issue 1-39 (1994-2000:Oct./Nov.); issue 40-43,45 (2000/2001:Dec./Jan.-June/July,Oct./Nov.); issue 46-66 (2001/2002:Dec./Jan.-2005:Apr./May); issue 69 (2005:Oct./Nov.)
American Grizzly. Issue 7 (1999:Aug.-Oct.)
Amsterdam in je kontzak. Edited by Erik Marcus and Paul Verstraeten. (1985)
Artweek v.32:issue 4 (John Rand artwork featured on page 22)
Bear. v.2:no.6 (1988); no.10-11 (1989-90); no.14-44 (1990-1997); no.46-63 (1997-2000); no.64 (2001:Apr.);no.65 (2009: Feb.);no.67 (2009:May-July)
Bear Cookin' The Original Guide to Bear Comfort Foods. By PJ Gray-Stanley Hunter. (2003)
Bear Fax. no.1-6 (1990)
Bear like me. By Jonathan Cohen. (2003)
Bears on Bears: Interviews and Discussions. By Ron Jackson Suresha. (2002)
Bears on Bears: Interviews and Discussions Revised Edition. By Ron Jackson Suresha. (2002)
Bearhug Quarterly. v.2:no.2-4 (1992:June - 1993:April)
Bears Prowl. no.1 (1990)
Big Ad. no.52 (1997:Jun.-Aug.)
Big Men's Quarterly Issue 6 April 2005 (John Rand photography featured on pages 41-47)
Bristlecone Peak. By Dave Brown. (1998)
Bulk Male. v.1:no.1-3 (1991); v.2:no.1-3 (1992); v.3:no.4-5 (1993:July/Aug.-Sept./Oct.); v.4:no.1 (1994:Jan./Feb.)
Canadian Male. no.1 (1996:Nov.); no.3 (1997:Mar.)
Contemporary gay american novelist. By Emmanuel S. Nelson. (1993)
Chiron Rising. Issue 58 (1993)